Cloud edge is a hype.
We do true edge.
We inject the software in the customer's windows distribution
Yo, what's up with the camera?
Dude, did you put Zoom on the microwave?
This was the microwave?
I finally found the CEO's email.
We can send the demo tomorrow.
I mean, I also have a social security number if you need it.
Yo, our network's down.
Perfect.
I was stress testing it.
Oh, did you see the new marketplace I rolled out?
What?
The demo we sent out to investors doesn't work.
I know, they're using Arc browser.
We don't need those investors.
I just came back from the meetup
on how to reduce our infra bill.
Yeah, infra bill is $0 somewhere.
Did you move our entire AWS stack to our Mac mini again?
You know how I'll be.
We had a working CUDA driver for Linux the whole time?
Hey man, have you heard GraphDBs?
What if you use graph?
Yeah.
Okay.
Yo, did you see this new AR library on Twitter?
Doesn't fit our use case.
It was out since today.
When have you tried it?
It's my library.
Is this Emacs and Temple OS?
Oh, this is Spacemacs.
Oh, what's this?
Don't touch this.
It's part of our infra.
You lost all our money on this CUDA cat?
Oh, it's back up.
We're rich.
Oh, I did rewrite the whole thing to Rust.
Oh.
I like the performance wasn't better,
so I wrote it back.
Or why don't we use it?
I already destroyed all the code and burned the computer.
What?
Yo, I wonder if I could write this in DeadFish.
No.
Fixed the coffee machine?
Patch the kernel?
Yo, not everything needs a kernel patch.
I just turn it on and off.
What is this?
Custom Linux.
Yo, our network's down.
No, no, no, it's a different one.
I ran the script I found online
and now the prod DB is missing.
Oh, don't worry.
We have a backup.
The whole backup.
Everything is gone.
Wait, I have a backup you didn't know about.
Can't trust humans.
This is our backup.
What about making it readable?
Who else needs to read this?
Oh, on the production website,
I added like a Homer button.
If you press it, you can see the customer statistics
all in one go.
It renders in 12.4 milliseconds.
People can see our customer statistics publicly?
Yeah, but it's super performant.
Man, it still isn't working on 360 videos.
We don't support 360 video.
We do in a few minutes.
How long do you think this is gonna take?
Three to five hours.
If you leave the room, maybe two.
Oh, is that your diploma?
What?
Oh, yeah, man, I need that for my visa.
Yo, I wrote the library from scratch.
What?
Yo, I wrote our own crypto.
Just to be safe.
We missed the deadline.
I sent it out 20 minutes ago already.
Did you want me to send the iOS or the Android version?
What?
The iOS version.
Oh, cool, I sent both.
What is this?
Oh, it's just I'm debugging in ASCII.
I'm not gonna waste resources.
We're two JavaScript frameworks away
from actually launching this.
What?
I'm joking, I'm joking.
It's all lost and hopeless.
What?
We need the feature today for the demo.
Hold on, my OS just broke.
Let me just fix it first.
Oh, actually, you know what?
I think it's just a Vulkan bug.
We don't need the UI.
We need the UI.
What?
Okay, okay, let's-
Isn't our demo on the PC?
Yeah, rip.
I'm horrible at coding.
Yo, what do you think about this UI design?
Oh, that's perfect.
How long to put in the app?
This is the app.
You're good at front end, too.
We need to raise money.
I put all our money in Bitcoin, we're good.
Cool, what else?
Dude, Metaverse is dead.
I already see with the guy who built it.
I'm trying to hire more engineers.
Just let me know which ones you want.
No, hire less engineers.
Less engineers.
Hire marketing people.
We need marketing people.
We already have 12.
Hire accounting.
We need accounting people.
What about product management?
Nah, all right.
Okay, it's PlayStation VM.
Written in Haskell.
No, SSL is a joke.
I know the guy who built the backdoor.
What backdoor?
What?
No, Solana is a joke.
I know the guy who's going to dump it.
What?
Oh yeah, forget that.
You're good at this, too.
Yeah, so when he kept saying crody,
that was actually like a Canadian reference.
Oh, actually what Kendrick Lamar meant
when he was talking.
Come on, man.
We need the demo in one hour.
It will be done by then, don't worry.
I got it, I got it.
I will be ready.
Oh, my OS just broke.
Just let me fix that first.
Come on, man.
Yeah, I'll be done by then.
Is this 2K25?
Yeah.
Limited edition?
Hijacked edition.
What does that say?
Oh, that's just compiler small talk.
It's red.
Compilers always be complaining.
Dude, new LLVM version and stuff.
Build is failing, though.
We have a demo coming up.
Ah, don't worry, I'll fix-